Hi, my name is Thomas Spear and one year ago
I almost choked to death on a tooth that fell
while I was asleep…
I was all alone in the dark bedroom…
With no one in the world to help me…
Hopelessly trying to gasp for air again and
again and again…
Until finally… somebody up there must have
really loved me…
I coughed… I coughed blood all over the
sheets and pillows…
And one tooth…
I never- not even in a thousand years –would
have thought such a thing is even possible…
But even though it was the most terrifying
experience from my entire life…
It was that precise nightmarish moment that
sent me on a completely unexpected journey
that opened my eyes to the sick and deadly
practices of the dental industry...
Helped me find out what’s really happening
inside the body when your gums are bleeding…
And eventually lead me to the discovery of
a completely natural and inexpensive method
that makes it possible for you to effortlessly
regenerate all your gums…
While super-cementing your teeth no matter
how advanced your tooth decay is...
In the following 5 minutes, I’ll show you
why…
Gum disease, tooth decay or bad breath
have nothing to do with how good your oral
hygiene is…
But with predatory bacteria buried deep inside
your gums, eating at your roots and spreading
like a plague to your throat, nose and airways…
And, no matter what your doctor tells you,
not even the deepest cleaning treatments can
reach and destroy these bacteria that are
tirelessly lurking inside your mouth even
when your teeth seem fine….
But, once you'll find out what you can do
about it, not only will you have the power
to get rid of your bleeding gums, bad teeth
and bad breath once and for all…
But you’ll also never have to face a dentist
for horrifying procedures again…
Because this solution is so simple that you
can use it right now in your own home in less
than 60 seconds…
And so incredibly powerful that it has been
clinically proven to work regardless of your
age, medical condition or the severity of
your tooth decay…
Without you having to spend a single red cent
on endless dental treatments, dangerous chemical-filled
medications... painful tartar removal, risky
surgeries, or implants.
In fact, this cheap method is so amazing...
That not only did it send shockwaves across
the medical establishment...
But many doctors see it as a miraculous key
that can unlock gum and teeth rejuvenation…
Yes, I know how incredible this sounds...
especially if you've been suffering from tooth
decay and terrible pain thinking there's NO
escape whatsoever...
But even if your dentist has crushed your
hopes by saying that “it’s too late”,
that you're bound to throw all your hard-earned
savings on teeth reconstruction and implants….
It's crucial that you stick with me until
the very end of my story, because in a few
moments....
You'll soon be able to save your teeth and
smile with confidence once again.
Just imagine…
No more throbbing pain, no more inflamed,
bleeding gums and bad breath…
No more risking serious infections or stuffing
yourself with medications hoping the pulsating
tooth agony will stop for just one second…
Never having to cover your mouth or feel embarrassed…
Instead eating whatever you want, whenever
you want…
Talking, smiling and taking pride in showing
your pearly whites….
Being able to kiss your wife or your kids
without seeing them turning their heads away…
And never ever having to set foot in a dental
office again.
Just like 57,000 other people did. People
like…
Nicolas C.J., 45 y. o., from Glendale, Arizona,
who wrote to say:
“I have always taken care of my teeth and
just couldn’t understand why my gums were
red, swollen and receding.
My dentist recommended me tartar removal,
it was awful, still hurts when I think about
that scaler digging under my gums. Not to
mention it didn’t help at all and one tooth
got loose.
Didn’t really believe in your method but
tried it anyway because I was desperate. It’s
like my gums have grown back. My teeth seem
whiter too. Thank you for this, never going
back to the doctor again!”
Or Kimberly M., 51 y. o., from Chicago, Illinois,
who says:
“Thomas, God bless you! I was sick with
worry over my teeth. I was spitting blood
every time I brushed and one of my front teeth
seemed to be moving. I hate dentists and I
sure didn’t have money for an implant. Now
everything is fine, gums are clean and healthy,
and no more loose teeth.”
Those are just two of the real life stories
from people just like you, who have already
used the method I'm about to share with you.
Now I'll give you all the details on how it
works in just a second.
But before I do, I want you to know who I
am…
Why my unusual discovery turned the dental
industry upside down while saving thousands
of people the pain and money of going through
implants and sickening dental procedures....
And how exactly it will help you rebuild your
teeth and gums in 60 seconds before going
to bed - even in the most severe of cases
of tooth decay.
So, as you know, my name is Thomas Spear.
I’m 52 years old and I live in a small town
near San Francisco, California, with my wife,
Hannah.
I’ve been a chemistry teacher for the past
30 years and, in the past 5 years, since my
wife had to retire early due to an accident,
I’ve also been working as a taxi driver.
Life’s never been too easy for me but I
don’t complain.
In fact, as you’re about to see, had it
not been for my two jobs, I wouldn’t have
come across the groundbreaking solution that
is now changing the lives of so many people…
You see, after getting my second job as a
taxi driver, I started working long hours,
especially at night, fuelling up on coffee
and sweets to stay awake or just find the
energy to carry on.
At first, I used to carry a toothbrush in
my glovebox and wash my teeth in gas stations
but after a while I was just too exhausted
for that.
Few months later, my gums started bleeding…
First time, I noticed the toothpaste I spit
out turned slightly pink...
Then, each time I got to brush my teeth, I
spitted out blood in the sink.
No big deal, I thought, I have more important
things to worry about.
A little bleeding from brushing can happen
to anyone,
nothing wrong with that, right?
Wrong, spitting out blood after brushing is
dead wrong...
It’s true, it happens to more people than
you think…
A whopping 56% of Americans suffer from some
form of gum disease…
But this does not make it any less serious…
You’re about to see inside this presentation
why you should never ignore this sign.
So, not long after, something embarrassing
happened.
At school, the other teachers kept turning
their heads away when I was talking to them…
Or just made a step back to keep a distance…
And once I’ve even overheard a few of my
students calling me “Beetlejuice”.
If you don’t know who that is…well, it’s
a movie character with rotten, horrible teeth…
When I heard them…
I just wished the ground would open and swallow
me.
I went to the bathroom and looked at my teeth
in the mirror.
Yellow, with swollen and irritated gums.
And as hard as it was to admit…
It was my breath that kept driving everybody
away.
Which explained why Hannah kept avoiding kissing
me or even hugging me.
But what really hurt like hell, was when I
wanted to take my granddaughter, Sarah, into
my arms, and she started crying:
“I don’t wanna! You make me vomit!”
Still, the worst was yet to come.
Pain.
Terrible, never ending, pulsating pain, even
after popping painkillers like Tic-Tacs.
I was always moody.
Always tired.
Avoided to talk to people as much as I could.
And on top of everything, my upper left molar
seemed to be moving.
It felt like in one of those bad dreams when,
you know, your teeth are falling…only it
was really happening…
My wife kept bugging me to go to the dentist.
On one side, I knew she was right, on the
other side…I kept postponing it…. and
eating only on the left side.
Listen, I’m a 6-foot tall man and I know
how this sounds…
But I’d rather pet a venomous, hairy, giant
tarantula than go to the dentist.
I get cold shivers up my spine just when thinking
about it…
The gruesome smells, the gut wrenching instruments.
But then…
The dreadful night came.
Hannah was babysitting our granddaughter,
so she was spending the night at our son’s
house.
I had a free shift so I was happy to get into
bed and finally get some sleep…
All seemed to be just fine, my gums weren’t
swollen anymore so I fell asleep with a glimpse
of hope…
…And got brutally woken up.
I’ll never forget the time: 12:47.
Choking, unable to breath, not knowing what
was stuck in my throat.
Hopelessly staring at the clock on the nightstand…
A minute that felt like eternity: from 12:47
to 12:48.
Then coughing up all the blood…and the molar.
I was sick to my stomach when I saw all the
mess.
Sick to my stomach when I thought I almost
died, choking on a tooth in my sleep.
The next morning, my cheek was swollen.
After hearing all that had happened to me
and seeing the way I looked, Hannah was worried
sick.
So, I knew I had no choice: I had to go to
the dentist.
My heart was pounding out of my chest when
I entered the cabinet.
After a quick look into my mouth and an X-ray…
The dentist gave me 2 frightening news….
And, please, keep listening, especially if
you’ve ever dealt with bleeding gums…
One. My gums were so damaged that I had passed
right by gingivitis, and landed into the dangerous
land of periodontitis.
Periodontitis is an advanced form of gum disease
that begins
with inflammation and bleeding…and ultimately
causes your gums to retract, your teeth to
fall, plus bad breath and tooth decay.
Not only that but gum disease and periodontitis
are also linked to
respiratory infections, kidney disease and
even oral deadly diseases.
All because- as you’re about to see- it
turns your mouth into a perfect environment
for harmful bacteria to thrive in…
So, what was I supposed to do? Well, as the
doctor put it…
Here’s how much it would cost you to “fix”
your gums at the dentist
and what you would have to go through….
Gum grafts… about $600 per gum, no guarantee
it will work. If your gums are seriously damaged,
this could cost you up to thousands of dollars.
Fillings and root canals to “save” the
teeth that were already damaged, with prices
that range from $500 to $2000- that’s a
lot of money for a lot of pain if you ask
me!
Then there’s surgery to “strengthen the
gums” or, in medical terms, “pocket elimination
surgery”, costs approximately $6,000…
Or – my favourite one- remove the worst
teeth and replace them with implants.
Thinking an implant costs $4,500 – best
case scenario- and that, according to the
doctor- I needed at least 4, I might as well
have sold one of my kidneys!
Oh, but the list doesn’t stop here… no
matter the dental procedure you choose as
your torture…
Know that after you’ll have to pay for…maintenance,
which can cost over $100 per session.
To put it bluntly: expensive, lengthy, painful
treatments that promised no real solution...and
I assure you, no doctor could ever guarantee
you that any of those treatments would work.
It’s all a game of chance: only it’s your
money, your time and your health on the table.
For example…
Did you know that you have to wait for a year
and a half to know if your dental implant
is a success or not?
Implants are usually a two-part process — first
putting in the implant, then waiting for the
area to heal and covering it with a crown
six to 3-4 months later…
And then, only if 1 year passes without infections
or other complications, can you finally breathe
a sigh of relief…
As if this depressing list wasn’t, the dentist
dropped the second bomb on me…
I needed surgery.
You see, my fallen tooth had a fractured root.
A piece of this root was still buried deep
inside my gums, causing an infection.
So, we needed to remove the remaining bits
and fast, before the infection was going to
spread even more.
As the doctor explained to me, a tooth infection
can “invade” your brain in a matter of
hours and lead to severe complications, and
even death.
Why? Because each one of your teeth is connected
to your brain through tiny nerves.
The infection can travel from the tooth to
the nose…to the eyes…and ultimately to
the brain.
Here’s how to tell if your infection
needs immediate medical attention
(1 tip I learned from the doctor)
If you experience confusion, headaches and
fever, you need to go to the hospital right
away.
As for my surgery, I’ll spare you the details.
Let’s just say getting stung with a big
anesthetic needle in your gums 5 times in
a row and then butchered for one hour straight
isn’t something you want to remember.
The most horrifying thing, however, was that,
even after the anesthetic from the surgery
was gone…
I couldn’t feel my chin and my mouth was
a little crooked.
It took me one month to recover and regain
the senses in my numb face.
Meanwhile I did a lot of research online to
see if anybody else had been in my situation…
Besides the only good advice I read… take
B vitamins for facial nerve recovery and pray
to God…
I came across a study that shattered me to
the core.
Dental procedures and surgeries- implants
included, can leave you disfigured.
No wonder they have you sign tons of consent
forms before the implant!
Anything to cover their backs in case something
goes wrong…
So, I could consider myself “a fortunate
case”.
After all these, one thing was sure: I was
never going back to the dentist again!
I started using a special toothpaste for gum
disease but with no success whatsoever…
I was afraid to chew, always checking my teeth
with my tongue to see if everything is fine…
I began eating mostly soups and mashed potatoes…
Until one day, it happened again:
One of my front teeth was moving.
That night I couldn’t sleep. I was paralyzed
with fear. And tormented by thoughts.
I was a full-grown man eating baby food
on his way to lose its front teeth, with no
money for implants,
and risking life-threatening infections.
That’s when I took the decision to take
the matter into my own hands and find a solution
that I could afford. Go to the end of the
earth if I had to. I couldn’t possibly live
like that.
So, I took some time off from teaching…which,
frankly, was a relief as I was too embarrassed
about my bad breath and bleeding gums to face
my colleagues…
And began spending my days in the biggest
library in San Francisco, searching every
corner…
As you can imagine, it was not easy... And
I can't tell you how many times I almost gave
up...
Well, there sure is a higher power out there,
because barely 3 weeks later, I FINALLY found
the one thing that changed everything...
That would end up giving me and over 57,000
other people just like yourself their good,
strong teeth and gums back.
Now, here’s what exactly happens inside
your mouth when you have gum disease…
It all starts with these dangerous bacteria
lurking deep inside your gums…
The bacteria are like small termites that
are relentlessly chewing on your teeth and
gums, leaving them bleeding and inflamed.
You might’ve gotten the bacteria from food,
water, or even from kissing or drinking after
somebody else.
In time, the bacteria, along with food debris,
multiply, accumulate and form the so-called
plaque and calculus.
The calculus/plaque is like a toxic mould
that spreads on your teeth walls, causing
bad breath and providing an “excellent”
home for the bacteria to thrive in.
Most of the times, your body’s natural defence
system succeeds in healing the swelling. But
there’s a catch to it: scars remain.
This means that, after every inflammation
episode, your gums retract.
Ultimately, they are too weak or too loose
to hold your teeth.
Not only that but another disturbing thing
happens…
(and you need to take action fast)
The next numbers are nothing less than frightening
but the good news is there’s a simple way
out of all of these and you’re going to
discover it soon.
According to a study conducted by the University
of Michigan…
There are 20 billion bacteria in your mouth.
These bacteria reproduce every 5 hours.
If you go 24 hours without cleaning your teeth
- and I’m going to show you the MOST efficient
way to clean your teeth inside this presentation-…
Those 20 billion become 100 billion!
And after they feed on your gums…
They start devouring the ligaments that hold
your teeth and supports the bones.
Your teeth loosen…
The roots get fractured…
And it’s only a matter of time until you’ll
face infections, throbbing pain and tooth
decay.
If you’re thinking –as I did back then-
all you have to do is “clean” your mouth
of bacteria…think again.
Here’s what I discovered next:
No dental or medical method
can destroy the gum-eating bacteria
(and here’s why)
This is not something you’re going to hear
from your dentist because they have no interest
in you knowing this.
Normally, doctors recommend brushing your
teeth at least twice a day, flossing or going
through dental scaling procedures to get rid
of the bacteria and tartar…
But here’s where it all goes wrong….
No matter how well you clean your teeth, at
least 10% of the bacteria will remain hidden
inside the “gum pockets”.
Why?
Because no traditional or advanced dental
cleaning method can reach that deep…
Electronic toothbrushes don’t stand a chance
of removing the teeth-eating bacteria as they
only deal with the surface of the teeth.
Dental floss might be good to clean the dental
debris but is very aggressive on your already
inflamed gums...
Mouthwash might cover the entire area and
go deeper under the gums but is not powerful
enough to break the plaque. Actually, all
it does is to attack your taste buds…
While dental scaling – the deepest method
of teeth cleaning- has to be done at least
once a week, often because the bacteria re-spreads
fast. But, if done too often, dental scaling
destroys the enamel. And without the enamel
protecting your tooth, you will scream with
pain, that I can guarantee.
Now, if your tooth falls, and you do have
the money for an implant and you’re also
lucky enough for the operation to be a success…guess
what?
The bacteria can always cause an infection
around the implant, resulting in inflammation
of the gums and, in the worst cases, leading
to bone loss in the jaw itself.
Plus, note that even if a tooth looks perfect
at the surface, the remaining 10% of bacteria
are still chewing on its roots.
Moreover…
Every time you do one of the following things,
the bacteria become even more resistant
1. Eating hard food. Yes, I know how that
sounds. But every time you take a bite, the
bacteria go even deeper. Why? Because you
put an incredible amount of pressure on your
teeth- up to 141 pounds!- therefore “sheltering
” the colony of termites deep inside the
gums.
2. Same thing happens at night if you’re
grinding your teeth. Chances you’re doing
during your sleep are very high as up to 50%
of Americans suffer from this condition, yet
few are aware of it.
So, what in the world could be powerful enough
to reach the bacteria, destroy it for good
and clean the plaque?
I was stuck. But not for long.
As I met one of the most respected medical
researchers:
Doctor S. T.
I’m using just his initials, to protect
his identity...
Anyway, S.T. came every morning into the library
and read tons of books on plants and herbs.
His smile was so perfect that I couldn’t
help but stare every single time he greeted
us.
One time I just couldn’t refrain myself:
“I’m sorry to bother you, but I couldn’t
not notice your teeth. I bet you had a lot
of work done…”
“Actually, none at all.”
So, we got to talking.
Dr. S.T. was retired for the past 2 years
and if he was to say the one thing he had
learned in all his 40 years of medical research
was that: plants were far superior to drugs.
His impeccable teeth were actually the result
of a homemade, soft “bubble gum” that
he’d been chewing on every morning.
Hearing all these, I began sharing my story.
The terrible night I almost choked to death
on my tooth, my gum disease and all the embarrassment
and pain it had caused me, the surgery…
And what I had discovered about the indestructible,
termite-bacteria…
“You know…”
Dr. S.T. said, after listening carefully to
my every word…
There’s one and only one thing that reaches
every corner of your mouth and goes under
your gums:
your saliva.
Seeing that I didn’t quite understand what
he was explaining, S.T. continued...
“The most important role of your saliva
is to protect your teeth and gums. That’s
why it has antibacterial properties and contains
lots of minerals and proteins.
That’s why the saliva is designed by nature
to reach every corner of your mouth and go
deep under your gums.
Meaning it has access- so to say- to all the
places where the bacteria thrive.
The only problem is…its power is limited.
And, without any help, it can’t possibly
break all the tartar or fight millions of
multiplying bacteria by itself.
Then, it hit me.
The solution:
turning saliva into the most powerful disinfectant
that would
break the tartar and destroy all the termite-bacteria.
But how?
After giving it some thought, S.T. came to
my rescue once again.
In his 40 years of medical research he had
seen certain herbs, plants and minerals 4
times stronger than morphine that could erase
migraines and tooth abscess pain…
Or anti-bacterial nutrients that made canker
sores outbreaks vanish in hours while forcing
the affected tissues to regenerate by the
next day…
The only thing was to find the right herbs,
plants & minerals that would perfectly mix
with the saliva and turn it into a strong
weapon against the termite-bacteria.
By now, you must be very curious and anxious
to find out what this ultimate teeth rejuvenation
solution contains...
Why it’s so extremely powerful that not
only does it fiercely fight gum disease and
tooth decay but it also starts the rebuilding
and rejuvenation of your teeth while protecting
you against other conditions, like cavities
and bad breath…
And, most importantly...
How does it work and why does it work
so incredibly well?
Please pay very close attention, because we
didn’t just discover a “trick” that
repairs your gums and teeth…
But something so incredibly powerful, that
not even Dr. S.T. believed to be possible…
And now, for the first time ever, we can share
the breakthrough secret of how this unique,
teeth-fortifying solution works:
We sourced a total of over 29 top ingredients
only from the purest locations, such as the
Alps mountains of Europe, the fertile plains
of India and western China, and from the best
plantations in South Africa, Ethiopia and
Kenya.
Moreover, after intensive lab testing, all
the powerful herbs, plants and minerals used
have proven to be 100% effective ONLY in this
formula, specifically calculated and adjusted
to be absorbed by your body, treating you
from the inside, and to supercharge your saliva,
making this ultimate dental weapon:
The FIRST STEP is to break the existing plaque
and tartar that have been loosening your gums
and creating a comfortable environment for
the termite-bacteria.
After more than 79 trials and experiments,
we have found out that the most effective
and fast way to do this was with the help
of Berberine.
This powerful antioxidant and anti-inflammatory
herb has been shown to fight harmful microorganisms,
including bacteria, viruses, fungi and parasites.
And since there are no side effects, Dr S.T.
said :
“It’s one ingredient and everyone both
under 40 or over should take - as the effects
are nothing short of a miracle.”
But because this is a very important teeth-rejuvenating
step, we added 2 more ingredients:
Turmeric - which is a well known antimicrobial
herb, proven to help remove plaque, bacteria,
and inflammation sometimes even more effective
than expensive traditional mouthwashes.
And Milk Thistle, which has been shown to
help treat damage to the liver caused by heavy
metals such as mercury, arsenic, cadmium,
and lead.
Why is that important?
Well, the answer is pretty simple: heavy metal
toxicity is a very serious issue, causing
even brain damage and most people are not
aware of this - but amalgam dental fillings
can contain up to 50% mercury.
That’s why Milk Thistle plays a very important
role in cleaning up and detoxifying your mouth
and body from these toxic metals.
The SECOND STEP is to locate the bacteria
colonies and destroy them by drowning them
in purifying substances that will also fight
the bleeding and inflammation.
Sounds simple enough, but I can assure you
it’s not.
That’s why we came up with a powerful trio,
consisting of Artichoke, Chanca Piedra - a
herb Dr. S.T. especially sourced from the
rainforests of South America and Red Raspberry.
These three ingredients are loaded with vitamins
and minerals like vitamin C, vitamin K, folate,
phosphorus, and magnesium, which act as essential
purifying agents and are especially important
for mouth infections.
The THIRD STEP - which is a crucial one, is
to tighten your loose gums, heal the wounds
and cement the teeth roots.
For this, we have used Yarrow - which, according
to the researchers from King's College London,
may increase fibroblasts, which are the cells
responsible for regenerating connective tissue
and helping your body recover from injury.
The second ingredient used to heal the wounds
is Beetroot.
Now, despite popular belief that Beetroot
stains your teeth, you should know that this
plant actually stops tooth decay, as recently
proven by the latest medical studies coming
from The Netherlands.
Your body converts beet root into nitric oxide,
which powers up your saliva’s healing properties,
and slows the growth of acid-producing bacteria
found in plaque.
The FOURTH STEP is to strengthen your teeth
crowns by filling them with minerals and vitamins.
This step is a lot like repairing cracked
walls.
The best ingredients to achieve this as fast
as possible are Dandelion, Alfalfa, Jujube
seeds and Zinc:
Dandelion greens provide a substantial amount
of several minerals, including iron, calcium,
magnesium and potassium
Alfalfa reduces sensitivity and strengthens
the teeth
The Jujube seeds, native from Southern Asia,
are particularly rich in vitamin C, an important
vitamin with high antioxidant and immune-boosting
properties
While Zinc is a trace mineral, and can naturally
be found in saliva. It has been proven to
fight against the growth of bacteria and plaque
and - here comes the best part:
Zinc is also needed for your senses of taste
and smell. And a Zinc deficiency can highly
reduce your ability to taste or smell.
Not anymore - as now you will be able to taste
a sizzling steak or a delicious lava cake
as if it was your very first time eating these!
The FIFTH STEP is to purify and detoxify the
gut and balance the mouth bacteria, with a
powerful blend of Chicory Root, Celery Seed,
Burdock Root and Yellow Dock.
All these plants also play a huge role in
reducing inflammation, and improving mineral
absorption for steel-strong teeth.
The SIXTH AND FINAL STEP towards a complete
oral rejuvenation is to form an impenetrable
shield for your teeth and gums, making them
virtually indestructible against future bacteria
or food debris.
To achieve this, we’ve added Grape Seed
Extract - which prevents the growth of common
foodborne bacteria, Ginger - which contains
gingerol, which is excellent at fighting off
bacteria and preventing infection and Feverfew
- which acts like a natural pain relief, without
the harmful side effects of common drugs.
And in order to take advantage of all the
latest discoveries in the field of medicine,
to our formula we’ve added some powerful
amino acids – such as Methionine and L Cysteine,
which play an essential role in your body’s
detoxification process.
No toxic substances in the body, no more infections,
right?
Back to this day I don’t know why S.T. agreed
to share and help me gather all the powerful
ingredients...
Maybe it was because of my story…
Maybe because of his passion for natural remedies…
Or maybe because, working in the medical industry,
he had seen enough dentists stuffing their
pockets with money and leaving innocent people
to faith after risky and expensive surgeries…
But one thing’s for sure: we made an amazing
team.
Him, a walking “natural alternatives Encyclopedia”…
Me, with all my knowledge on chemistry, ready
to test every possible interaction between
the saliva and the various plants and herbs
he had discovered…
We worked night after night, testing until
dawn inside S.T.’s home laboratory…
Making sure that we got the right quantities
and the most effective combination of ingredients....
And there were times when I was so tired that
I could throw up but, in the end, there it
was: a solution that gathered all-powerful,
100% natural herbs, plants, minears and anti-bacterial
nutrients.
Of course, I was the very first one to try
it.
After the first day, I didn’t feel a thing.
Well, maybe hope, which was still something
I thought that I'd lost forever!
But when I woke up the second morning, something
had clearly changed.
There was no more blood after brushing. I
just couldn’t believe that- for the first
time in months- I wasn’t spitting blood
like in a horror villain.
The following days I just could believe my
eyes: more than half of the plaque had disappeared…
And soon after that, my heart stood still:
my front tooth wasn’t moving anymore.
Seeing my progress, I gathered a list of 20
people I knew who suffered from various forms
of gum disease and asked them to discreetly
test out our formula.
Every single person accepted immediately,
especially because no one needed to leave
their house, as we personally delivered them
all the selected teeth-fortifying ingredients.
They each received a daily report form to
follow their progress.
I was prepared to wait at least a week for
the initial reports to come back.
But what happened next was amazing...
Even after 3 or 4 days, I was getting call
after call
from everyone in the study, claiming
their gums and teeth felt like new
They were stunned.
I was even more SHOCKED at how quickly my
gum swelling and tooth pain went away…
Honestly, when I woke up one morning and felt
no ache, and no metallic taste in my mouth…I
thought for a second that I was dead!
Faster than I thought, my gums had tightened
back up and completely re-attached to my teeth…
And soon, it was like my gum disease had never
happened. Plus, the shade of my teeth was
a lot lighter…
Not only that but, according to my wife, I
wasn’t grinding my teeth in my sleep anymore…
My life was completely normal again! I could
finally smile, eat whatever I pleased…and
nobody would ever judge me for how my teeth
looked!
And it wasn't just me...
When I went to collect the reports from the
other subjects in my initial study...
The results I saw were astounding!
Not a single person reported tooth pain, gum
inflammation, plaque or bad breath…
And most importantly: no loose teeth.
Even Dr. S.T. had seen nothing like it.
It was clear we couldn't keep this life-saving
protocol all to ourselves…
All the suffering had to end!
And we needed to make our discovery accessible
to as many people as possible.
So, we created a clinically proven and all-natural
supplement available for anyone who's tortured
by gum disease or tooth decay.
We’ve called it:
Steel Bite Pro
The 100% natural solution that you can use
to rebuild your gums and teeth starting today.
Once all the bacteria are destroyed, Seel
Bite Pro will help you to…
· Stop bleeding and receding gums, while
you regain their healthy look and feel...
· Stop the pain and infections (this alone
will save your thousands in painful root canals
and other dental bills);
· Make the ugly plaque build-up literally
fall shed away your teeth;
· Escape gingivitis and periodontal diseases;
· Get rid of bad breath and all the embarrassing
moment caused by it;
· Enjoy the confidence of having whiter teeth,
without cavities;
· Never have to throw your savings on dental
implants and risk nerve damage or even facial
paralysis…
· And never, ever have to go to the dentist.
To create Steel Bite Pro, we’ve sourced
only the purest, highest quality 23 plants,
herbs, minerals and vitamins, measured the
exact quantities needed and put them into
an easy to swallow capsule to take once a
day.
Every capsule is manufactured in the USA,
in our FDA approved and GMP certified facility,
under sterile, strict and precise standards,
so you can be 100% sure it’s safe, clean
and of the highest quality.
Moreover, Steel Bite Pro capsules are non-GMO.
They do not contain any dangerous stimulants
or toxins, and they are not habit forming.
Not only is Steel Bite Pro revolutionary in
its approach…
But it can be used by anyone, at any age,
regardless of their medical condition…
Even after years of neglect and decline.
To date, more than 57,000 Americans just like
you have already used the Steel Bite Pro personally,
or shared it with a loved one.
And across the board, the results are incredible:
Here’s what Gabriel Backer, 40 y. o., from
Baltimore, Maryland says:
“No more bleeding gums and I still can’t
believe I got rid of cavities! And to think
how easy it was. I’ve been using Steel Bite
Pro for three weeks now and I’ll share it
with everyone I know!”
Or Loretta Martin, 48, New Orleans, Louisiana,
who says:
“I was afraid to eat. Always cut everything
into tiny pieces and chewed them carefully.
After just one week of Steel Bite Pro, I finally
had the courage to eat my favourite food:
beef steak. It was a huge victory for me.”
And Dameon Sanders, 52, Flint, Michigan, who
says:
“I don’t think there’s a worse pain
than tooth pain. I couldn’t focus at work
or enjoy my free time and I was hooked on
painkillers. Now it’s like I’ve got my
life back. No more pain, it just feels so
good.”
All you have to do in order to achieve the
same life-changing results is to start using
it as soon as possible.
The solution is much simpler than you’d
think.
And you can get access to everything in the
next 90 seconds.
Now, knowing all of this, it's obvious why
Steel Bite Pro dominates any other option
to “fixing” gum disease…
Nothing else out there proved to WORK...
Instead, Steel Bite Pro is a completely natural
and 100% effective way of destroying the dangerous
bacteria that are now lurking deep inside
your gums, sentencing you to tooth decay…
Of course, you could go to a dentist, who
will torture you with sick plaque cleaning
methods like dental scaling…… methods
that can’t reach the root cause of your
gum disease and eliminate the termite-bacteria…
Or maybe he'll talk you into expensive, lengthy
treatments like gum grafts or pocket elimination
surgery... treatments that no doctor can guarantee
they work - and good luck getting your insurance
to cover the costs of thousands of dollars!
Next, your doctor might suggest you to replace
your worst teeth with implants that cost $4,500
a pop, and have you wait one-and-a-half years
just to see if the operation was a success…not
to mention the termite-bacteria can still
cause an infection around the implant.
You could put your hopes inside special toothpastes
or fake “gum strengthening” creams- but
these will never be strong enough to be that
cure-all you're wishing for.
All are a waste of money, time, and energy
and you know it!
They won't get you well in a million years...
Unlike Steel Bite Pro that can get the job
done in less than three weeks while keeping
your gums and teeth safe from future dental
disorders…
You can understand why Dr. S.T. and I initially
wanted to set the value for Steel Bite Pro
at $399.
That’s less than a gum graft surgery…
And certainly a lot less than the cost of
a dental implant…
Plus, with Steel Bite Pro you don’t run
the risk of infections or even face nerve
damage as it’s 100% natural and side-effect
free…
When you think about all of that, it should
be pretty clear why both I, and the more than
57,000 people who have already used Steel
Bite Pro personally… think that $399 is
a steal.
But This Is Not About Us Making A Profit
I’ve seen firsthand how using the Steel
Bite Pro gave me my life back, got me rid
of all the pain and humiliation….
And how I don’t have to lose sleep at night
worrying about whether one of my teeth will
fall or not, whether there’s an infection
that could spread to my brain and kill me
in a matter of hours…
Plus, I know the desperation of being sick
and broke…with no money to take care of
yourself…
Which is why I’m not going to ask you to
invest anywhere near the $399 I was initially
going to price this at…
Or even $299, or $199, or heck even $99.
Instead, and only while this website remains
online… which may not be that long given
the incredible threat it poses to big pharmaceutical
companies and dental conglomerates…
You can get your very own 30-day supply of
Steel Bite Pro
for a one-time 100% risk free investment of
$69.
That’s right. Just $69!
Before you order, one last thing: after thoroughly
researching all the ingredients of Steel Bite
Pro, and running dozens of tests - I recommend
you take this supplement for at least 90 days.
On one hand, it’s about giving your body
enough time to process and take full advantage
of all the plant extracts and steadily locate
and destroy every single colony bacteria.
This way, your teeth could absorb all the
minerals and nutrients, thus undoing years
and years of dental damage...
On the other hand, Steel Bite Pro is selling
incredibly fast and, once it will be sold
out, it will take us at least 6 to 9 months
to produce a new batch.
Not only because we’re accepting only the
purest ingredients but also because when an
ingredient is clinically proven to work so
well - like Berberine, Big Pharmaceutical
Companies buy up all the supplies of this
plant and pretend it’s for “research”
purposes.
They offer such a high price for it that it’s
creating an artificial shortage.
Berberis, the shrubs from which Berberine
is extracted is incredibly hard to find in
the wild.
And even if there are a few Berberis farms
out there, even fewer of them grow it without
using chemicals, while most of them are filling
their pockets right now thanks to pharma companies
buying up all their crops years in advance.
You might find it in bottles in a health food
store, but those supplies aren’t pure, or
they skimp on quality control to make up for
their lost profits from the high ingredient
cost.
So yes, you can consider yourself lucky if
Steel Bite Pro is still in stock today.
But you know what?
I want you to take full advantage of how great
Steel Bite Pro is, and, at the same time,
save as much as you can on your health investment!
So I'm going to make the deal even sweeter:
Because I know how hard it is to live with
throbbing teeth pain, inflamed, bleeding gums
and bad breath…
I've set up a discounted package system of
6 bottles of Steel Bite Pro for you, for only
$49 dollars a bottle, for a total of $294
which is being offered TODAY ONLY... for as
long as supplies last. You also get free shipping
on us.
Once we run out of bottles, the "BUY NOW"
buttons will not be active anymore until we
make another batch again (which takes around
2-3 months at least).
Click the 6-bottle package (or any other package
that you want) below to secure your order.
Consider this the smallest, but most powerful
investment that you have ever made for yourself!
Yes, 1 bottle of Steel Bite Pro might stop
bleeding and receding gums, while you regain
their healthy look and feel.…
3 bottles might be enough to rapidly stop
the pain and infections, saving you thousands
of dollars in painful root canals and other
dental bills AND remove all the ugly plaque
build-up from your teeth…
But 6 bottles of Steel Bite Pro will tighten
your loose gums and cement the teeth roots,
strengthen your teeth crowns and turn your
saliva into a super strong shield for your
teeth and gums, making them virtually indestructible
against future bacteria or food debris!
You may be saying,
“OK, this sounds amazing and I'm interested!
How do I get started?”
Click the buy button below after choosing
the best package for you, and you'll end up
on our secure checkout page. Enter your payment
details, place the order... and in 7 days
from this moment, you'll get Steel Bite Pro
delivered to your home!
BUT CLICK NOW, IT’S THE ONLY WAY SECURE
YOUR PACKAGE WHILE SUPPLIES LAST!
You have absolutely nothing to risk because
you are also covered by our 60 Days
"100% Healthy Or Money Back" Guarantee.
Here’s how it works…
You simply say “maybe” to the Steel Bite
Pro today by clicking the “Buy Now” button
below.
Once you’ve done that, the most important
step into completely rejuvenating your teeth
& gums is practically done!
And, if you don't start seeing incredible
and dramatic improvements…
All you need to do is contact us within the
first 60 days from your purchase. It doesn’t
matter if you used up the entire bottle, we
will still give you your money back.
This means you have 2 whole months to decide
if Steel Bite Pro is for you or not.
No hidden fees or subscriptions. Just a safe
and secure one-time simple payment.
Remember: you’ll still have a full 60 days
to decide whether or not the Steel Bite Pro
is for you or not. I’m taking all of the
risk here, and it doesn’t bother me one
bit.
I want to help as many Americans as I can,
which means making it as easy as possible
for you to try this today.
So, go ahead, choose your package and say
“maybe” by clicking the “Buy Now”
button below right now.
But please, know you really do have to act
now.
We are offering Steel Bite Pro for an amazing
price just to get this amazing solution into
more hands.
But we are planning on raising the price to
$99, or possibly much higher in the future.
Because here's the weird thing:
When I tell people that you can easily fight
gum disease and tooth decay… in practically
no time and for less than the price of an
electric toothbrush...
Well, most people think it's unbelievable,
as if there's something "fishy" going on.
But our mission is to spread Steel Bite Pro
to as many people as humanly possible, and
the big dream is for gum disease and dental
clinics to be a thing of the past!
But, if people find it hard to believe that
you can get such incredible results and destroy
life-threatening bacteria for less than a
meal with your family at a restaurant, then
we'll have to raise the price.
Not to mention we don't know how much longer
we'll be able to hide from Big Pharma's threats.
But if this website is still up, it means
you can still get the Steel Bite Pro if you
act now.
So, click the button below to place your order
now.
Listen, when you think about it, you really
have only two choices ahead of you right now:
Option one: Stop following this presentation
and leave this page. Do nothing. Keep going
the way you are now, with your gums always
sore and inflamed, risking life-threatening
infections and diseases.
Live in pain, fear and embarrassment... for
months, maybe even years, or decades. It's
not going to be pleasant.
Option two: Risk nothing at all today. Grab
Steel Bite Pro right now. And you'll be surprised
at how well it works.
So choose your package and then just click
the button below:
… Still here?
That's fine, this letter covered so much information
that it’s only natural you have some questions.
Let’s take a quick moment to answer some
typical questions asked by clients before
they choose the Steel Bite Pro…
1. How and why does Steel Bite Pro work?
Well the way this works is pretty simple actually…
Gum disease, tooth decay or bad breath have
nothing to do with how good your oral hygiene
is, but with a life-threatening bacteria buried
deep inside your gums, eating at your roots
and spreading like a plague to your throat,
nose and airways.
No teeth cleaning method can reach the places
where the dangerous bacteria hides, and the
only substance that can reach the bacteria
hiding place is your saliva.
The only solution is to turn your saliva into
an incredibly powerful disinfectant & teeth
strengthener by using natural but extremely
potent ingredients.
This method is really inexpensive and has
no side-effects and works incredibly well!
2. Is this protocol for everyone?
Yes! Steel Bite Pro is non-invasive, risk-free
and was designed for people of all ages and
medical conditions.
3. When should I take Steel Bite Pro ?
We recommend you take 2 capsules each day,
with a big glass of water. You can take them
whenever you feel comfortable - either in
the morning, afternoon or even in the evening,
if you had a busy day and forgot about it.
4. What kind of results can I expect to see?
More than 57,000 people have now used the
Steel Bite Pro, and the results have been
remarkable. However, It depends on how quickly
your body responds to the ingredients used
in the protocol. Some people see changes faster,
while others may take longer.
So, please allow at least three weeks to see
a dramatic improvement.
5. How long will this program be available
for?
I can’t give you an exact answer here.
I want it to stay up forever, however the
pharmaceutical companies are becoming increasingly
hostile towards me, and starting to make threats.
As soon as my family is at risk – I’ll
have to take the site down. That means you
really should get this program right now,
especially since there is zero risk to you,
as I’ll explain in a second…
6. What’s with that guarantee again?
So, the reason there is no risk for you is
that you have a full 60 Days to try the Steel
Bite Pro for yourself.
If, for any reason over the next two months
you’re not satisfied, you simply send me
an email (I’ll provide my address inside)
and I’ll immediately refund your entire
investment with no questions asked. No dentist
will ever do that.
7. I'm ready to buy! What do I do now?
This one is easy: Simply choose your package
by clicking on one of the options below, and
try out the entire program for yourself, for
60 days, with absolutely no risk. If you are
unhappy for any reason, you'll be given a
prompt refund, no questions asked...